Guide to the Louis Gottschalk Papers [ca. 1927]-1975
University of Chicago Library
- Series IV: Student Papers
  - Student Files, Ta-Ti, Tannenbaum, Edward Robert Thatcher, Harold W. Thomas, Franklin V. Tihany, Leslie C. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Student Files, Wa-We, Waldo, Gary Warth, Robert D. Watson, David S. Webb, Norris K. Webster, T. S. Weintraub, Karl Joachim Werlin, Joseph Sidney (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Student Files, Wi-Y, Williams, Russell Williston, Frank G. Wolfson, Philip J. Young, Anne P. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Lafayette Term Papers, Notes on paper on Lafayette (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Lafayette Term Papers, Anonymous Anonymous (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Acomb, Frances, Amann, Peter Apt, Leon (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Bailey, Charles R., Barnard, Jack Boyd, Julian P. Burks, K. Moser-3 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Calkins, Kenneth, Carey, Raymond G. Cates, William H. Centner, Charles W.-2 Curtis, Eugene N. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Fagg, John, Featherstonhaugh, Arthur C. Fietze, Ella (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Ford, Ford, Richard Freyham (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Glazier, Ira A., Godfrey, Eleanor E. Smith-2 Goodman, Gordon L. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Horning, Carol, Isherwood, Robert M. Jefferson, Carter-2 Kessler, Larry (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Lach, Donald-2, Lansing, Augusta Logue, William Lyon, E. Wilson (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - McNeil, G., Mears, John Morning, Carol Moser, Margaret Nechelas, Ruth F. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Parry, Albert, Philips, Craig-2 Pircher, Frances-2 Students' Paper (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Smith, Catherine Haugh-2, Spencer, Frank-3 Stewart, Gordon (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Thomas, Franklin V., Thomas, Hester Ann Vernon, H.A. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Weintraub, K. J.-7 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Williams, Patrick A., Wilson, John H. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Al-Ar, Alfonso, Oscar M. Apt, Leon Armerding, Hudson T. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Ar-As, Arnold, Doan F. Asch, Walter Ashton, John (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Be-Bo, Benkoil, Mair J. Bone, Christopher Borzo, Henry (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Cal-Cap, Calinger, Ronald Calkins, Kenneth Cappadacia, E. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Ch, Chapin, W. Chen, Min-sun (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Co-Cu, Couse, Frances S. Connell, Sr; Marie Joan Curry, George (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Da, Dannenfeldt, Karl H. Davies, David R. Dawson, Charles H. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Du, Duncan, T. Bentley Dunlap, Neil Butler (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Fa-Fea, Fajn, Max Featherstirchaugh, Arthur C. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Fe-Fu, Fennell, Josephine Friend, Julius W. Fulkerson, Stephen (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Ga-Gl, Gasman, Daniel Glagov, Sylvia (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Go, Goldstein, Morton E. Gould, S. W. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Ha-He, Haas, Arthur G. Hanser Herr, Richard (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Hi-I, Himmelfarb, Gertrude Isherwood, Robert (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, J-Ku, Jefferson, Carter Klein, Martin Kutolowski, John F. (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, La-Leo, Labelle, Dale Leonard, Tamis W. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Lew-Lo, Lewalski, Kenneth F. Loenenfeld, Eva Logue, William (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Ma-Mee, Maddox, Margaret Meehl, William (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Men-Ph, Mendelson, Saul Philips, Craig (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Ra-Rea, Rapoport, Marie Rearick, C. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Ren-Ro, Renaldo, John J. Roth, Jack J. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Sch, Schmidt, R. J. Schmitt, Haus A. Schroeder, Richard (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Si-Sp, Simons, Richard B. Simonson, David Spiegel, Paul M. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, St-Sw, Stevenson, Thomas H. Stone, Bernard B. Swecker, Zoe (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Ta-Va, Tannanbaum Trostle, Robert R. Van Kley, E. Varga, Botand (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Wa-Weber, Warth, Robert D. Webb, Morris K. Weber, William (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Webster-Wilson, Webster, T. S. Weiss, Stuart White, Bob Wilson, John H. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Wilson-Wind, Wilson, Prince E. Windhausen, John (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Student Files, History 408/50, Wood-Young, Woodward, M. Young, Anne (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - History 408/508 universal history approach, Ap-Ba, Appel, David N. Bailey, Charles R. Bailey, Stephen Barbagallo, Carrado (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - History 408/508 universal history approach, Fi-Gr, Fisch, Gerald M. Grathwol, Robert Gross, Hanns (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - History 408/508 universal history approach, Ho-Mears, Holmes, Oliver Kern, Paul Mears, John (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - History 408/508 universal history approach, Mer-On, Mershart, Ronald V. Moorhus, Roger Onwumelu, John (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - History 408/508 universal history approach, Sl-Wa, Slavenas, Julius P. Stevens, Eric T. Thomas, Donald Waldo, Gary (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Courses, Student Work, An-Bl, Annes, Raymond P. Alexander, Roberta Sue Beatty, E. C. O. Blackwood, George D. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Courses, Student Work, Carey, Carey, Raymond G. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Courses, Student Work, Cate-Fain, Cate, James Lea Cates, Jane Lohrer Cronk, Antoinette Fajn, Max (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous Courses, Student Work, Gh-Ly, Ghobar, Ash Hartshorne, E. Y. Jr. Himmelfarb, Gertrude Kreiser, B. R. Lehman, Warren W. Lyon, E. Wilson (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Courses, Student Work, Mc-Mo, McFadyen, Christiana Meade Mershart, Ronald V. Morgan, Victor (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Courses, Student Work, N-R, Newman, Edgar Padover, Saul K. Puzzo, Dante A. Ross, James Bruce (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous Courses, Student Work, Sa-Si, Santillaner, George Schmidt, Royal J. Schuster, E. M. Sipek, George-2 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Courses, Student Work, Sl-Su, Slusser, Robert Smedley, Katherine Summer, Imogene-2 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Courses, Student Work, Th-Wy, Thomas, Franklin V. Welsh, James Wrinkler, Henry R. Wycott, J. Earle (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Bibliographies by Students, A-B (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Bibliographies by Students, C-E (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Bibliographies by Students, F-H (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Bibliographies by Students, I-M (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Bibliographies by Students, N-R (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Bibliographies by Students, S-Z (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Donald B. Sanger, "An Introduction to the Military History of the United States." (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Donald B. (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Series V: Lafayette Studies, Correspondence
  - Owners of Lafayette materials. 1930-40. A-E (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Owners of Lafayette materials. F-G (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Owners of Lafayette materials. H-J (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Owners of Lafayette materials. K-M (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Owners of Lafayette materials. N-R (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Owners of Lafayette materials. S-Z (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Owners of Lafayette materials. 1941-42 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Owners of Lafayette materials. 1943-46 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Owners of Lafayette materials. 1947-73 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Dealers in America and England (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Dealers in America and England (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Dealers in France, 1930-34 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Dealers in France, 1930-34 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Comte de Chambrun (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - John F. Gough, 1940 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - John F. 1940. 1940-45 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - John F. 1946 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Stuart W. Jackson, September-December, 1930 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Stuart W. April-July, 1931 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Stuart W. August-December, 1931 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Stuart W. January-April, 1932 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Stuart W. May-July, 1932 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Stuart W. August-December, 1932 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Stuart W. Jackson, 1933 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Stuart W. 1933. Jan-Apr, 1934 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Stuart W. 1933. May-Dec, 1934 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Stuart W. 1933. Jan-Jul, 1935 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Stuart W. 1933. Aug-Dec, 1935 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Stuart W. 1933. Jan-Jun, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Stuart W. 1933. Jul-Dec, 1936 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Stuart W. 1933. Jan-Jun, 1937 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Stuart W. 1933. Jul-Dec, 1937 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Stuart W. 1933. Jan-May, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Stuart W. 1933. Jun-Dec, 1938 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Stuart W. 1933. 1939 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Stuart W. 1933. Jan-Jul, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Stuart W. 1933. Aug-Dec, 1940 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Stuart W. 1933. 1941 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Stuart W. 1933. 1942 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Stuart W. 1933. 1943-45 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Stuart W. Jackson, 1946-47 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Stuart W. 1946-47, 1948 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Stuart W.1946-47, 1950-57 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Walter P. Gardner, Oct. 1930-31 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Walter P. Jan-Sep, 1932 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Walter P. Oct-Dec, 1932 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Walter P. 1933 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Walter P. 1934 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Walter P. Gardner, 1935 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Walter P. 1936 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Walter P. 1937 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Other Lafayette amateurs, 1930-38, A-M (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Other Lafayette amateurs, N-Z (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Other Lafayette amateurs, 1939-49 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Other Lafayette amateurs, 1950-56 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Other Lafayette amateurs, 1957-64 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Other Lafayette amateurs, 1965-75 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Minutes of the Second Bureau of the Assembly of Notables, February 24-March 6, 1787 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Index of Ball Collection (microfilms in Series X) (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Bonaventure Collection (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Gottschalk's notes on Bouille's letters to Lafayette, nos. 21-31 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Office of M. le Comte Rene de Chambrun, July 1971 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Mimeographed catalogue...Drouot...1956 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Notes on Espinchal taken by Mile. Yacoels (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Catalogues of the Fabius Collection by G. W. Pierson and H. C. Rice (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - French newspapers (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - La Grange Collection-1956 clippings (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Newberry Library-list of Lafayette pamphlets (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Theodore E. Norton (Lafayette College and Friends of Lafayette) (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Observations du General Lafayette (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Translations of the Tougard letters in possession of Dr. Frederick, Prime (131 E. 66th St., N.Y.C.) (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Archives-United States (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Library of Congress, Archives of War Department, 1930-34 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Library of Congress and National Archives (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Library of Congress and National Archives (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Government documents (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Masons and Masonic organizations (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Historical societies (Box 43, Folder 3-7)
  - Libraries and museums (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - State and public libraries (non-university), 1935-43 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - State and public libraries (non-university), 1945-67 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Foreign libraries and archives, 1929-32 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Foreign libraries and archives, 1933-61 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - State and public universities and colleges, 1930-34 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - University and college libraries, 1935-45 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - University and college libraries, 1946-60 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - University and college libraries, 1961-74 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Libraries and librarians-miscellaneous, 1930-35 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Libraries and librarians-miscellaneous, 1936-40 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Library lists of Lafayette material, Part I (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Library lists of Lafayette material, Part II (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence in re Lafayette material (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Follow-up letters (Box 44, Folder 8-9)
  - American Friends of Lafayette,. 1931-32 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - American Friends of Lafayette,. 1933 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - American Friends of Lafayette,. 1934-39 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - American Friends of Lafayette,. 1960-73; programs and pamphlets, 1938-40 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - American Friends of Lafayette (Box 45, Folder 5-6)
  - Reviews; Lafayette Studies (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - A survey of published Lafayette letters (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Lafayette Bicentennial (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Bicentennial Lafayette clippings, Part I (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Bicentennial Lafayette clippings, Part II (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Newspaper clippings on Lafayette, Part I (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper clippings on Lafayette, Part II (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper clippings on Lafayette, Part III (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper clippings on Lafayette, Part IV (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, etc. Part I (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, etc. Part II (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Lafayette Papers Project, 1970; exhibit publications on Lafayette by Cornell (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Lafayette Papers Project, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Lafayette Papers Project, January-May 1972 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Lafayette Papers Project, June-December 1972 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Lafayette Papers Project, January-June 1973 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Lafayette Papers Project, July-December 1973 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Lafayette Papers Project, January-April 1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Lafayette Papers Project, May-December, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Lafayette Papers Project, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Guide manuscript; chronological outline of Lafayette's career (Cornell project) (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Guide manuscript (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous parts of Guide (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Oversize material related to Professor Gottschalk's research on Lafayette Includes genealogies of Lafayette. as well as six broadsides privately printed by Erich O'D. Taylor, entitled Campaign on Rhode Island MDCCLXXVIII (Box 47a, Folder 1)
- Series VI: Photostats
  - Duplicates. Through 1782 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Duplicates. 1783-99 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Duplicates. 1800-25 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Duplicates. 1826-death of Lafayette (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Uncertain date Filed under proper names, addresses, etc. A-G (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Uncertain date Filed under proper names, addresses, etc. H-W (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Uncertain date Arranged according to days of week or month (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Photostats up to and including February 1777 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - March 1777-September 1777 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Oct-Dec 1777 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - January 1778 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - February 1778 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - March 1778 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - April 1778 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - May 1778 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - June 1778 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - July 1778 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Aug-Oct 1778 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Nov-Dec 1778 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Jan-Feb and uncertain date, 1779 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Mar-Apr 1779 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - May-Jun 1779 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Jul-Aug 1779 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Sep-Oct 1779 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Nov-Dec 1779 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Jan-Feb and uncertain date, 1780 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Mar-Apr 1780 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - May 1780 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - June 1780 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - July 1780 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - August 1780 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Sep-Oct and uncertain date, 1780 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - November 1780 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - December 1780 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - January 1781 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - February 1781 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - March 1-15, 1781 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - March 16-31, 1781 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - April 1-15, 1781 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - April 16-30, 1781 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - May 1-10, 1781 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - May 11-20, 1781 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - May 21-25, 1781 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - May 26-31, 1781 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - June 1-10, 1781 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - June 11-20, 1781 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - June 21-30, 1781 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - July 1-10, 1781 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - July 11-20, 1781 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - July 21-25, 1781 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - July 26-31, 1781 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - August 1-10, 1781 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - August 11-20, 1781 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - August 21-31, 1781 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - September 1781 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - October 1781 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - November 1781 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - December 1781 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - January 1782 and uncertain date (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Feb-Mar 1782 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Apr-May 1782 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - June 1782 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - September 1782 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Oct-Dec 1782 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Jan-Feb 1783 and uncertain date (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Mar-Jun 1783 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Sep-Oct 1783 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Nov-Dec 1783 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Jan-May 1784 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Jun-Sep 1784 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Oct-Dec 1784 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Jan-Mar 1785 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Apr-May 1785 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Jun-Sep. 1, 1785 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Sep-Dec 1785 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Jan-Feb 1786 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Mar-June 1786 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Jul-Dec 1786 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Jan-Mar 1787 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Apr-Jun 1787 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Jul-Sep 1787 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Oct-Dec 1787 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Jan-Mar 1788 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Apr-Dec 1788 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Lafayette Emigre-Renseignements sur les creances de le Clerc-dont le titre est encroye a 1'agence. November 1788-29 August 1792 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Proces Vesbaldu Comite Militaire, Part I (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Proces Vesbaldu Comite Militaire, Part II (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Proces Vesbaldu Comite Militaire, Part III (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Jan-Jun 1789 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - July 1789 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Aug-Sep 1789 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - October 1789 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Nov-Dec 1789 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Jan-May 1790 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Jun-Aug 1790 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Sep-Dec 1790 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Jan-May 1791 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Jun-Aug 1791 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Sep-Dec 1791 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - January 1-17, 1792 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - January 18-31, 1792 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - February 1792 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Mar-Apr 1792 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - May-Jul 1792 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - August 1792 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Sep-Dec 1792 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Jan-Jun 1793 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Copy of Memoires de LaFayette from Papers of Library of Congress [?], June 20, 1793 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Jul-Dec 1793 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Jan-Jun 1794 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Jul-Dec 1794 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Jan-Dec 1795 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Jan-Apr 1796 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - May-Dec 1796 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Jan-Jun 1797 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Jul-Nov 1797 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - December 1797 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Jan-Jun 1798 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Jul-Dec 1798 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - January 1799 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Feb-Jun 1799 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Jul-Aug 1799 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Sep-Dec 1799 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Jan-Dec 1800 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Jan-Dec 1801 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Jan-Dec 1802 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Jan-Jun 1803 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Jul-Dec 1803 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Jan-Jun 1804 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Jul-Dec 1804 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Jan-Jun 1805 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Jul-Dec 1805 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Jan-Dec 1806 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Jan-Dec 1807 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - 1808-1809 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Jan-Dec 1810 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Jan-Dec 1811 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Jan-Jun 1812 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Jul-Dec 1812 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Jan-Dec 1813 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Jan-Jun 1814 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Jul-Dec 1814 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Jan-Dec 1815 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Jan-Dec 1816 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Jan-Dec 1817 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Jan-Dec 1818 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Jan-Dec 1819 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Jan-Dec 1820 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Jan-Dec 1821 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Jan-Dec 1822 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Jan-Dec 1823 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Jan-Jul 1824 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Aug-Sep 1824 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Oct-Dec 1824 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Jan-Feb 1825 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Mar-Jun 1825 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Jul-Aug 1825 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Sep-Dec 1825 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - American Farmer 1826-1833 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - January 1826 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Feb-Jun 1826 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Jul-Sep 1826 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Oct-Dec 1826 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Jan-Jun 1827 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Jul-Dec 1827 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Jan-Mar 1828 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Apr-Aug 1828 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Sep-Dec 1828 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Jan-Apr 1829 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - May-Jul 1829 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Aug-Dec 1829 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Xeroxes from books on 1830 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Jan-Mar 1830 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Apr-Jun 1830 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Jul-Sep 1830 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Oct-Dec 1830 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Jan-Mar 1831 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Apr-Jun 1831 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Jul-Sep 1831 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Oct-Dec 1831 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Jan-Feb 1832 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Mar-Apr 1832 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - May-Aug 1832 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Sep-Dec 1832 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Jan-Jul 1833 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Aug-Dec 1833 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Jan-May 1834 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Jun-Dec 1834 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - After 1834 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Sparks Mss, Vol. I, XXXII, pp. 96-149. [L.G. Comp. W. Memoires.] (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Sparks Mss, Vol. I, XXXII, pp. 96-149. Pp. 150-212 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Sparks Nss, LXXXVI, Part III, pp. 194-209 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- Series VII: Audiotapes
  - World Affairs Conference, October 29, 1958, "France and World Tensions," University of Omaha (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Causes of Revolution, October 28, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Japan lectures, Side 1; Unesco World History, May 3, 1968 Side 1 & 2; Lafayette in 1789, May 4, 1968 Side 2; General Problems of Historical Composition, May 5, 1968 Side 2; The American Revolution and the French Revolution, May 7, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Tsuda College, Japan, May 1968 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - "American and French Coustitutions; Agnes Scott College, April 8, 1959 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Series VIII: Notes
  - January 1778-September 1778 (Box 68)
  - October 1778-April 1780 (Box 69)
  - May 1780-January 1781 (Box 70)
  - February 1781-May 1781 (Box 71)
  - June 1781-September 1781 (Box 72)
  - October 1781-March 1783 (Box 73)
  - April 1783-December 1784 (Box 74)
  - January 1785-March 1787 (Box 75)
  - April 1787-July 1789 (Box 76)
  - July 1789-October 1789 (Box 77)
  - October 1789-February 1790 (Box 78)
  - February 1790-June 1790 (Box 79)
  - July 1790-September 1790 (Box 80)
  - October 1790-January 1791 (Box 81)
  - February 1791-April 1791 (Box 82)
  - May 1791-June 1791 (Box 83)
  - July 1791-November 1791 (Box 84)
  - December 1791-April 1792 (Box 85)
  - May 1792-June 1792 (Box 86)
  - June 1792-July 1792 (Box 87)
  - August 1792 (Box 88)
  - August 1792-December 1793 (Box 89)
  - 1794-August 1797 (Box 90)
  - September 1797-1801 (Box 91)
  - 1802-1813 (Box 92)